noiseaddicts.com 2011-09-28

# Upload, Showcase, and Share Music on Twitter

## Search Music by Genre

## Search Music Title/Desc

## Audio File Tags

## Popular Articles

## Interesting Articles

## Information Collected:

This "site" (noiseaddicts.com) collects information from you when you visit the site, fill out a form, upload content, email us, or interact with other users.. 

## Purpose of Information Collected

Information collected may be used is any of the following ways: 

  * To ensure proper site operation
  * To provide you with a service
  * To improve the site
  * To send requested information

## Protection of Information

The site implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of personal information.

Your private, personal information is not for trade or sale. We value your privacy.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if your settings and preferences allow it) that enables the site or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to save your preferences, help with security and navigation, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer a better site experience. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating the site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce the site policies, or protect ours or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor and traffic information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Third party links

At our discretion, the site may include or offer third party products or services on the site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

This site and it's services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## Terms and Conditions

The use of this website does NOT constitute legal or financial advice. Please consult with a professional who understands your individual situation in order to receive personalized and appropriate help. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Policy

If we decide to change our policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the modification date below. 

**Last Updated: 09/01/11**
